YAREMA OSTROVSKYI



Contacts

Github

in Linkedin

yaremaphoto@gmail.com

> +38 (096) 367 66 54

Languages

Ukrainian

Russian

English - Intermediate (B1)

Interests

Technologies

Photography

Art

Yoga

Hiking

Longboard

Storytelling

Summary

Frontend developer with 6 months of commercial experience in React. Used JavaScript for more than 1 year and half years on TypeScript. Worked with domains: E-commerce, Education, Fintech. Can work on remote. With spiker English.

Skills

HTML5	JavaScript	Redux toolkit
CSS3	TypeScript	Eslint
Sass	React	
Git	Redux	

Experience

Frontend developer at Softteam

06/2021-09/2021

Job responsebility:

Assist the development manager in working on software design and coding. Attend and contribute to company development meetings. Participation in conversations and build plan tasks. Update and learn new coding skills. Write and maintain code. Work and monitor minor bug fixes and the technical performance of internal systems. Respond to requests from the development team. Gather information from consumers about program functionality. Write reports. Conduct development tests. Chatting and meeting with clients, teams, and mentor.

Frontend developer at ATC-267 Art-tech.charity

09/2021-11/2021

Job responsebility:

Build MVP product for a startup. Estimate tasks. Development from the beginning product. Developers structure app. Working with team Involvement with Web3, Dapps, Moralis, Solidity technologies; Preparation of the UI part for connection with the crypto-wallet, De-Fi and NFT Conversations with the foundering project. Build an app on React-toolkit, RTK-query Add and styling features and new tools (searching, filtering, creating a topic, changes on server part, responsibilities screen, module windows, tips...) Build testing JSON-server Work with rest APi Implementing UI mockup with Bootstrap and CSS modules. custom save on localStorage Git merge branching versions Deploy on Heroku

Education

High-school at Ukrainian Academy of Print (Lviv) 2010 - 2014

Multimedia Electronic Publications

master degree

HactoberFest-2021

Coderetreat-2021

Bootcamp at ELEKS *24/03/2021- present*

Public repositories:

<u>Currency converter</u>

Fintech app has few features of conversion currency -change date, count, history and graphs

Constructor projects

SPA. App can build project with discription, photo and video view on gallery. Project have able edit and delete. Common features- searching

Game square

Game click on the squares. It has three levels of difficulty. Responsive to the screen